<vtydoc xmlns='urn:osmocom:xml:libosmocore:vty:doc:1.0'>
    <node id='21'>
    <child_of nodeid='4' />
    <name>SGSN Configuration Node</name>
    <description>Configure the remote GGSN, access-control and other
    attributes of the SGSN</description>
	<command id='gtp local-ip A.B.C.D'>
	<description>
		Configure the local IP address to which the SGSN should
		bind for the Gp interface (towards the GGSNs).

		Please note that in case you would like to run the GGSN
		on the same machine as the SGSN, you can not run both on
		the same IP address.  It is suggested to use 127.0.0.1
		for the SGSN and 127.0.0.2 for the GGSN in such
		situations.
	</description>
	</command>
	<command id='ggsn &lt;0-255&gt; remote-ip A.B.C.D'>
	<description>
		Configure a static GGSN with a given numeric identifier
		to use the specified remote IP address.
	</description>
	</command>
	<command id='ggsn &lt;0-255&gt; gtp-version (0|1)'>
	<description>
		Configure whether to use GTPv0 or GTPv1 towards the
		specified GSSN number.
	</description>
	</command>
	<command id='ggsn dynamic'>
	<description>
		Enable dynamic resolving of GGSNs based on DNS resolving
		the APN name like in a GRX-style setup.  Changing this
		setting requires a re-start of the SGSN.
	</description>
	</command>
	<command id='grx-dns-add A.B.C.D'>
	<description>
		Use the specified IP address for DNS-resolving the AP
		names to GGSN IP addresses
	</description>
	</command>
	<command id='apn APNAME ggsn &lt;0-255&gt;'>
	<description>
		Map the given APN Name to the given GGSN number.
	</description>
	</command>
	<command id='apn APNAME imsi-prefx IMSIPRE ggsn &lt;0-255&gt;'>
	<description>
		Map the given APN Name to the given GGSN number _only_
		if the IMSI matches the given prefix.
	</description>
	</command>
	<command id='imsi-acl (add|del) IMSI'>
	<description>
		Add or delete the given IMSI to/from the global Access
		Control List.
	</description>
	</command>
	<command id='auth-policy (accept-all|closed|acl-only|remote)'>
	<description>
		Configure the Authorization policy of the SGSN.  This
		setting determines which subscribers are permitted to
		register to the network.
	</description>
	</command>
	<command id='gsup remote-ip A.B.C.D'>
	<description>
		Set the IP address of the HLR (gateway) for the GSUP protocol.
		This setting only applies if auth-policy remote is used.
	</description>
	</command>
	<command id='gsup oap-id &lt;0-65535&gt;'>
	<description>
		Set the OAP client ID for authentication on the GSUP
		protocol.
		This setting only applies if auth-policy remote is used.
	</description>
	</command>
	<command id='gsup oap-k K'>
	<description>
		Set the OAP shared secret key K for authentication on
		the GSUP protocol.
		This setting only applies if auth-policy remote is used.
	</description>
	</command>
	<command id='gsup oap-opc OPC'>
	<description>
		Set the OAP shared secret OPC for authentication on the
		GSUP protocol.
		This setting only applies if auth-policy remote is used.
	</description>
	</command>
	<command id='access-point-name NAME'>
	<description>
		Globally allow the given APN name for all subscribers.
	</description>
	</command>
	<command id='cdr filename NAME'>
	<description>
		Set the file name for the call-data-record file,
		logging the data usage of each subscriber.
	</description>
	</command>
	<command id='cdr interval &lt;1-2147483647&gt;'>
	<description>
		Set the interval (in secodnds) for the call-data-record
		file.
	</description>
	</command>
    </node>
</vtydoc>
